http://www.afbrisbane.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

French coursesAdultsKids and teensPrivate and a la carte tuitionCorporateTest and ExamsFAQWhat's onFrance eMotion exhibitionFrench Christmas Gift ShopWine TastingChristmas RaffleLe Story TimeCulture chez vousLe Book ClubAlliance Francaise French Film FestivalMembershipBecome a MemberCulturethèqueMédiathèque LibraryFrench ChoirBring a Friend GiftFrench ChatsMembers DiscountServicesStudy in France - CampusFranceGift VoucherMeeting room for hireTranslation ServicesBookshopMerchandiseSchools2020 song and poetry competitionSchool VisitsDELF Prim & JuniorStudent Exchange with AFXFrench for TeachersCourses in Schools and Childcare CentresAbout UsAf NetworkTeamPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsEmploymentContact UsOur partners2020 Notice of AGM
Login
Receive Our Newsletter
MenuFrench coursesAdultsKids and teensPrivate and a la carte tuitionCorporateTest and ExamsFAQWhat's onFrance eMotion exhibitionFrench Christmas Gift ShopWine TastingChristmas RaffleLe Story TimeCulture chez vousLe Book ClubAlliance Francaise French Film FestivalMembershipBecome a MemberCulturethèqueMédiathèque LibraryFrench ChoirBring a Friend GiftFrench ChatsMembers DiscountServicesStudy in France - CampusFranceGift VoucherMeeting room for hireTranslation ServicesBookshopMerchandiseSchools2020 song and poetry competitionSchool VisitsDELF Prim & JuniorStudent Exchange with AFXFrench for TeachersCourses in Schools and Childcare CentresAbout UsAf NetworkTeamPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsEmploymentContact UsOur partners2020 Notice of AGM
Privacy Policy
General
The Alliance Française de Brisbane will only collect personal information from you with your prior knowledge and consent. You can
browse our website without disclosing personal information.
Computer information
Our service provider makes a record of your visit and logs the following information, for statistical purposes, for each page accessed the:
IP (Internet Protocol) address of the machine which has accessed it;
Top-level of your domain name;
Address of your server;
Date and time of your visit to the site;
Pages accessed and documents downloaded;
Previous site visited;
Type of browser and operating system you have used.
No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities except, in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law
enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider’s logs.
Navigation data
Browsing any website – including the Alliance Française de Brisbane website – generates a trail of pages visited and the
time apparently spent displaying each page.
User feedback
We seek feedback from our users in order to improve the service offered by the site. Answering feedback questions is voluntary and does not
in any way affect your access to the Alliance Française de Brisbane website.
Data storage and disclosure
Information collected is stored in an appropriately secure format and held by the Alliance Française de Brisbane for archival
purposes. When the information is no longer required for the purposes for which it was collected it is deleted.
The data is used by the Alliance Française de Brisbane website software, and by staff involved in the operations, only for:
- Website and system administration, including monitoring to prevent security breaches;
- Customisation of the website to user needs;
- Evaluation, research and development.
Email newsletters
The Alliance Française de Brisbane uses its email newsletters to notify subscribers of events or opportunities. Individuals must
register as subscribers for this service and your details will only be known to the Alliance Française de Brisbane staff and will be
disclosed to a third party only in circumstances in which such disclosure is legally authorised, such as in the investigation of a criminal
offence and in compliance with a search warrant or subpoena.
E-commerce website
Customer service is fundamental to our business. As part of this service we may use your personal information to offer you products and
services that may benefit you. As part of the registration process a customer may elect not to receive any marketing material. Customer
details and delivery addresses are collected for the purposes of supplying goods to customers and providing after-sales service.
The Alliance Française de Brisbane e-commerce website protects your credit card details. This ensures that your credit card details are seen only by yourself and the bank performing the transactions. No credit card details are captured or stored by the Alliance Française de Brisbane e-commerce site.
Contact Us
Alliance Francaise de Brisbane
262 Montague Road,
West End, QLD 4101.
